{
    "id": "7ac68f3d4c1e4616a87b7fd9012aa232",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is oily ..................... but she does not have a kind heart.",
            "description": "Oily tongued means excessively smooth-spoken",
            "answers": [
                "skinned",
                "tongued"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can I borrow some milk?’ ‘Why not? We have ...................... and some to spare.’",
            "description": "To have more than enough.",
            "answers": [
                "a lot",
                "enough",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t depend on him. He is a man of ..............................",
            "description": "Used to refer to a person who has a weak character",
            "answers": [
                "feather",
                "straw",
                "red"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We were already going through a financial crisis so dad's illness was a bolt from the ……………………….",
            "description": "A sudden and unexpected event that is usually harmful.",
            "answers": [
                "sky",
                "hell",
                "blue"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Her refusal to answer his phone calls was a red rag to the .........................",
            "description": "An act or utterance that is going to provoke someone.",
            "answers": [
                "tiger",
                "elephant",
                "bull"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "After wasting two hours searching for the cat, we realized we were on a wild ........................... chase.",
            "description": "A wild goose chase is a search that is completely unsuccessful.",
            "answers": [
                "cat",
                "goose",
                "crow"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When the business failed, years of hard work went up in ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "vain",
                "smoke",
                "smog"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is every ......................... a gentleman.",
            "description": "Every inch means thoroughly.",
            "answers": [
                "ounce",
                "pound",
                "inch"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He thinks he is highly influential but he is actually a big ....................... in a small pond.",
            "description": "When you are a big fish in a small pond, you have a lot of influence only over a small area.",
            "answers": [
                "turtle",
                "frog",
                "fish"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Giving advice to this worthless fellow is like casting pearls before a .........................",
            "description": "To cast pearls before a swine is to talk wisely to fools.",
            "answers": [
                "dog",
                "monkey",
                "swine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a tough guy and will weather any ……………………….",
            "description": "To weather a storm is to face difficulties. ",
            "answers": [
                "tornado",
                "hurricane",
                "storm"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}